vflyer.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | vFlyer

## vFlyer Inc. Privacy Policy

#### This privacy policy applies to the entire site of [www.vflyer.com](http://www.vflyer.com/).

vFlyer Inc.  
201 Post St, STE 800  
San FranciscoCA94108  
US  
800.594.5930 x1  

We respect your privacy. This is why we have taken the time to disclose our information collection practices and our privacy policy. Please take time to review this document carefully. 

**We collect information for the following purpose(s):**

  * Enabling the creation and management of marketing content
  * Tailoring the site for its visitors
  * Enabling the usage of this service
  * Contacting our visitors for promotion of the site or products

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us such as name, address, phone, billing information; either via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. automatically submitting listing data to marketplace partners. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you in the future to tell you about special offers, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

**What control do you have over this information?**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our site:

  * See what data we have about you, if any
  * Change/correct any data we have about you
  * Have us delete any data we have about you
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data

**What type of security policies are in place to protect sensitive information?**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the site, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

If you believe that our site has collected incorrect information or if you would like to dispute any information, please contact us using the address at the top of this page.
